Guide to the Frank H. T. Rhodes papers,1977-1996.
Rhodes, Frank H. T. papers, 1977-1996.
- Series VI. 1982-1983
  - Provost's Office
    - Office of the Provost
      - Office of Equal Opportunity, 1978-84 (Box 83, Folder 24)
        Montgomery, Michael; Rivera, Ramon E.
      - College Advisory Council Reports, 1977-81 (Box 83, Folder 25-26)
      - Library Advisory Council, 1982-84 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Colleges
      - Statutory Colleges General, 1980-83 (Box 83, Folder 28)
        "Academic I;" faculty salaries.
      - College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1982-83 (Box 83, Folder 29)
        Cooperative Extension.
      - Cornell Plantations, 1982-83 (Box 83, Folder 30-31)
      - College of Architecture, Art and Planning, 1982-83 (Box 83, Folder 32)
      - College of Arts and Arts and Sciences College of Arts and Sciences, 1981-83 (Box 83, Folder 33)
      - Performing Arts Center, 1982-83 (Box 83, Folder 34)
      - Society for the Humanities, 1981-83 (Box 83, Folder 35)
      - Social Science Coordination, 1976-83 (Box 83, Folder 36-37)
        Sociology.
      - Statistics, 1979-83 (Box 83, Folder 38)
        Study of Division of Mathematical Science.
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1983 (Box 83, Folder 39)
        Name change; Public and Health Administration Programs.
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1982-83 (Box 83, Folder 40)
        Strategic Task Force. Public and Health Administration Programs.
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1982-83 (Box 83, Folder 41)
        Strategic Task Force; Yale University. Public and Health Administration Programs.
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1978-79 (Box 83, Folder 42)
        Seidman Washington Proposal.
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1983 (Box 83, Folder 43)
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1982-83 (Box 83, Folder 44-45)
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1982 (Box 83, Folder 46)
        Strategic Task Force.
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1982-84 (Box 83, Folder 47-48)
        Elimination of Public and Health Administration Programs.
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1982-83 (Box 83, Folder 49)
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1982 (Box 83, Folder 50)
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1982 (Box 84, Folder 1-6)
      - Business and Public Administration (Graduate School of Management), 1982-83 (Box 84, Folder 7-13)
        Reorganization.
      - College of Engineering, 1982-83 (Box 84, Folder 14-15)
      - College of Engineering Dean Review, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 16-17)
      - Graduate School Doctoral Program, 1978-83 (Box 84, Folder 18-20)
        Education.
      - School of Hotel Administration, 1982-83 (Box 84, Folder 21-22)
      - New York State College of Human Ecology, 1982-83 (Box 84, Folder 23)
      - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1982-83 (Box 84, Folder 24)
      - Law School, 1982-83 (Box 84, Folder 25)
      - Division of Nutritional Sciences, 1982-83 (Box 84, Folder 26)
        Savage Hall addition.
      - New York State College of Veterinary Medicine, 1982-83 (Box 84, Folder 27)
        Otisville Facility.
      - New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Dean Review, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 28-35)
        Melby, Edward C., Jr.
    - Faculty
      - Dean of Faculty, 1978-83 (Box 84, Folder 36)
      - Statutory Budget Committee, 1977-83 (Box 84, Folder 37)
        Faculty salaries.
      - Calendar, 1979-83 (Box 84, Folder 38)
      - Deans' Council, 1982-83 (Box 84, Folder 39-40)
      - Deans' Council, 1982-83 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Membership, 1981-82 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Searches
      - Graduate School of Management Dean Search, 1983-84 (Box 85, Folder 3-5)
      - Graduate School of Management Dean Search, 1981-84 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Graduate School of Management Dean Search, 1983-84 (Box 85, Folder 7-11)
      - Graduate School of Management Dean Search, 1979-83 (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - Graduate School of Management Dean Search, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - Graduate School of Management Dean Search, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 14-17)
        Spencer Stuart & Associates.
      - Graduate School of Management Dean Search, 1981-84 (Box 85, Folder 18-22)
      - Architecture, Art and Planning Dean Search, 1983-84 (Box 85, Folder 23-25)
      - Architecture, Art and Planning Dean Search, 1983-84 (Box 85, Folder 26)
        McMinn, William G.
      - Architecture, Art and Planning Dean Search, 1983-84 (Box 85, Folder 27-33)
  - Subject Files
    - Associations
      - Miscellaneous, 1982-83 (Box 85, Folder 34-37)
      - Association of American Universities, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 38)
        National Science Foundation; Report of the AAU Committee on the Integrity of Research.
      - Association of American Universities, 1982-83 (Box 85, Folder 39-40)
      - Association of American Universities, 1982-83 (Box 85, Folder 41)
        Department of Health and Human Services; Department of Defense.
      - Association of American Universities, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 42-43)
      - Association of American Universities, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 44)
        Graduate education and research.
      - Association of American Universities, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 45-46)
      - Association of American Universities, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - American Council on Education, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 2-4)
        Commission on International Education.
      - American Council on Education, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - American Council on Education, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - American Council on Education, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - American Association of University Professors, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - Association of Governing Boards of Colleges and Universities, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - Associated Universities, Inc., 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1981-83 (Box 86, Folder 12-16)
      - Consortium On Financing Higher Education, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 17-20)
      - Consortium On Financing Higher Education, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 21)
        Financial Issues in Graduate Education and an Agenda for Research.
      - Consortium On Financing Higher Education, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 22)
      - Consortium On Financing Higher Education, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 23)
        "Uncapping" of retirement.
      - Five Associated University Libraries, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 24)
        Dissolution.
      - Ivy Council of Presidents, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 25-27)
      - Ivy Council of Presidents, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 28)
        Hockey eligibility.
      - Ivy Council of Presidents, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 29)
      - Ivy Council of Presidents, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 30)
        Parallel football league.
      - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 31)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 32)
        Marine Division; Draft registration and financial aid.
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 33)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 34)
        Department of Health and Human Services.
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 35)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges:, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 36)
        Higher Education and Technology Committee.
      - Seven Universities Group, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 37)
      - TIAA/CREF, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 38-39)
      - Universities Research Association, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 40)
    - Corporations
      - Miscellaneous, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 41-42)
      - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 43)
        Holmes, D. Brainerd. Raytheon Company.
      - Committee for Corporate Support of Private Universities, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 44)
      - Amoco Foundation, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 45)
      - Atlantic Richfield Company, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 46)
      - Bell Laboratories, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 47)
      - Continental Group, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 48)
      - Deloitte Haskins and Sells, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 49)
      - Dupont de Nemours and Company, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 50)
      - Emerson Electric, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 51)
      - Exxon Corporation, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 52)
      - General Electric Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 53)
      - General Motors Corporation, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 54)
      - Gulf Oil Corporation, 1982-83 (Box 86, Folder 55)
      - Hewlett Packard, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Hewitt Associates, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - IBM, 1981-83 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 4)
        Cornell Biotechnology Institute.
      - Mobil Oil Corporation, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - New York Telephone, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Procter and Gamble Company, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - RCA Corporation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Rohm and Hass Company, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Shell Companies Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - Standard Oil Company of Ohio, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Sybron Corporation, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - Union Carbide Corporation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - Fellowships and Scholarships, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Foundations
      - Miscellaneous, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 15-17)
      - Atlantic Richfield Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 18)
        Geological Sciences Building
      - Atlantic Foundation, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 19-21)
      - Atlantic Foundation, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 22)
        Excellence in Teaching proposal; undergraduate education.
      - Atlantic Foundation, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 23)
        International Education Program.
      - Atlantic Foundation, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 24-26)
        Rhodes' presentation on Higher Education.
      - Carnegie Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 27)
      - Phelps Dodge Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 28)
      - Exxon Education Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 29)
      - Ford Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 30)
      - Guggenheim Foundation, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 31)
      - Hewlett Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 32)
      - Kellogg Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 33)
      - Knight Foundation, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 34)
        Center for International Studies; Center for Performing Arts; Writing Program.
      - Knight Foundation, 1981-83 (Box 87, Folder 35)
        Gibson, C. C.
      - Kresge Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 36)
        Center for Performing Arts.
      - MacArthur Foundation, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 37)
      - Mellon Foundation, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 38)
      - Mellon Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 39)
      - Mellon Foundation, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 40)
        New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center.
      - Mellon Foundation, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 41)
        Hatfield, Robert S.; New York Hospital - Cornell University Medical College.
      - National Science Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 42)
      - Pew Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 43)
      - New York State Science and Technology Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 44)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 45)
      - Seeley G. Mudd Fund, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 46)
      - Sloan Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 47-48)
      - Sloan Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 49)
        College of Engineering.
      - Teagle Foundation, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 50)
    - Higher Education
      - General, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 51)
      - Federal Funding, 1981-83 (Box 87, Folder 52)
        Bankhead-Jones Act.
      - Miscellaneous Bills, 1982-83 (Box 87, Folder 53)
      - Miscellaneous Bills, 1980-82 (Box 87, Folder 54-56)
      - Miscellaneous Bills, 1980-81 (Box 87, Folder 57)
      - Miscellaneous Bills, 1979-80 (Box 87, Folder 58-61)
      - Miscellaneous Bills, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 62)
        Hazing
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1980-81 (Box 87, Folder 63-65)
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1982-83 (Box 88, Folder 1-4)
      - State Education Department, 1982-83 (Box 88, Folder 5-7)
      - New York Public Interest Research Group(NYPIRG), 1982 (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - Department of Education, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 9)
      - Advisory Council on Postsecondary Education, 1982-83 (Box 88, Folder 10-12)
    - Universities
      - Miscellaneous, 1982-83 (Box 88, Folder 13-18)
      - Miscellaneous, 1982-83 (Box 88, Folder 19)
        Research University Consortium.
      - SUNY, 1982-83 (Box 88, Folder 20-22)
        Cornell/State relations.
      - SUNY, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 23)
      - SUNY, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 24)
        Agricultural and Technical Colleges.
      - SUNY, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 25)
      - SUNY, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 26)
      - SUNY, 1982-83 (Box 88, Folder 27)
        Cornell/State relations; SUNY/Cornell visits.
      - SUNY, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 28)
        Wharton, Clifton R. Jr.; Cornell/State relations.
      - SUNY, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 29)
        Wharton, Clifton R. Jr.; Tuition.
      - SUNY: Master Plan, 1981-83 (Box 88, Folder 30)
      - SUNY Master Plan, 1981-82 (Box 88, Folder 31)
        College of Environmental Science and Forestry; Cornell/State Relations.
    - Student Life
      - Glee Club, 1982-83 (Box 88, Folder 32)
      - Rhodes' Scholarship, 1974-81 (Box 88, Folder 33)
      - Miscellaneous, 1982-83 (Box 88, Folder 34)
    - Campus Affairs
      - Incidents, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 35)
        Solidarity Day
    - Commencement
      - General, 1982-83 (Box 88, Folder 36-37)
- Series VII. 1983-1984
  - Presidential/Administrative
    - Office of the President
      - General Correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 88, Folder 38-40)
      - General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 41)
        England trip.
      - General Correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 88, Folder 42-44)
      - General Correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 1-2)
      - General Correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 3)
        Nuts.
      - General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 4)
        Smithsonian Institution.
      - General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 89, Folder 6-7)
      - General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 8)
        European trip.
      - Condolences, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - Congratulations, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 10-14)
      - Congratulations, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 15-16)
        Academic promotions.
      - Emeritus Professors, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 17)
      - Presidential Councillors, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 18)
      - Presidential Councillors, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 19)
      - Presidential Councillors, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 20)
      - Presidential Councillors, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 21)
      - Presidents Emeritus, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 22)
      - General Contact, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 23)
      - Contact - Departments, 1982-84 (Box 89, Folder 24)
      - Employee Contact, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 25)
      - Faculty Contact, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 26)
      - Student Contact, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 27-28)
      - Student Contact, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 29)
        Minority students.
      - Social Events, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 30-35)
      - Social Events, 1982-84 (Box 89, Folder 36)
      - Social Events, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 37-43)
      - Social Events, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 44)
      - Social Events, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 45-50)
    - Executive Staff
      - General, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 51)
    - Assistant to the President
      - General, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 52)
        Barlow, J. Robert
      - Federal Relations, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 53)
      - Federal Relations, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 54)
        Subcommittee on Postsecondary Education.
      - Federal Relations, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 55)
      - Judicial Advisor, 1983-83 (Box 89, Folder 56)
      - Ombudsman, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 57)
    - Senior Vice President
      - General, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 58)
        Collegetown.
      - General, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 59)
        Armory.
      - General, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 60)
        Retirement Community.
      - General, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 61)
        Cornell Club of New York Facility.
      - Budget, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 62)
      - Budget, 1981-83 (Box 89, Folder 63)
      - Budget, 1982-83 (Box 89, Folder 64)
      - Budget, 1984-85 (Box 89, Folder 65)
      - Budget Discussion Papers, 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 66)
      - Budget Discussion Papers, 1977-80 (Box 89, Folder 67-69)
      - Office of Personnel Services (OPS), 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 70-72)
      - OPS - Fringe Benefits, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 1-3)
      - OPS - Fringe Benefits, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 4)
        Cornell Children's Tuition Scholarship Program special commitments.
      - OPS - Middle Management, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - OPS - Personnel Data, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - OPS - Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 8-12)
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 13)
        Kennedy, Laing E. Athletic Director search.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 14)
        Athletic Director search.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 15)
      - Salaries, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - Controller, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 17)
      - Bursar's Office, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 18)
      - Payroll Office, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 19)
      - Responsibility Centers Analysis, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 20)
      - Office of Personnel Services (OPS) - Collective Bargaining, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 21-23)
        History of United Auto Workers (UAW) and Cornell.
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 24)
        Gray, Edward F.; Fraser, Douglas A.; History of UAW and Cornell.
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 25)
        Gray, Edward F.; History of UAW and Cornell.
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 26)
        Carey, Hugh L.; New York State Legislature. History of UAW and Cornell.
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1980-81 (Box 90, Folder 27-30)
        History of UAW and Cornell.
    - University Counsel
      - General, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 31)
        Litigation report.
      - General, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 32-35)
      - General, 1981-83 (Box 90, Folder 36-39)
      - State Relations, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 40-45)
      - State Relations, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 46)
        Murphy, Cecil L.; United Food and Commercial Workers Union; Geneva Experiment Station employee relations.
      - State Relations, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 47)
        Molisani, Howard; Sheinkman, Jack; Labor relations; Right-to-Know law.
      - State Relations, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 48)
        Stern, William; Weinshall, Iris; New York State Urban Development Corporation.
      - State Relations, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 49)
      - State Relations, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 50)
        Sub-cabinet on Education.
      - State Relations, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 51)
        Gold, Emanuel R.
      - State Relations, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 52)
        Dormitory Authority of the State of New York Staff Report for Financing of Cornell University.
      - State Relations, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 1)
        Alumni legislative support.
      - State Relations, 1983-84 (Box 90, Folder 2)
        Albany Legislative Reception.
      - State Relations, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 3-4)
        Siegel, Mark Alan; Barbaro, Frank J.; Labor relations.
      - State Relations, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Senior University Counsel, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 6)
        Stamp, Neal R.; University Bylaw Revision Project.
      - Senior University Counsel, 1978-83 (Box 90, Folder 7-8)
      - Senior University Counsel, 1979 (Box 91, Folder 9)
        Stamp, Neal R.; Collection of delinquent student loans.
      - Senior University Counsel, 1980-83 (Box 91, Folder 10)
        Stamp, Neal R.; Board Study Committee. University Bylaw Revision Project.
      - Senior University Counsel, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Senior University Counsel, 1979-80 (Box 91, Folder 12-15)
      - State University Statute, 1978-79 (Box 91, Folder 16-19)
        SUNY Legislative Project.
      - State University Statute, 1978-79 (Box 91, Folder 20)
        Wharton, Clifton R., Jr.; SUNY Legislative Project; Cornell/SUNY relations.
      - State University Statute, 1977-79 (Box 91, Folder 21)
        SUNY Legislative Project; Cornell/SUNY relations.
    - Treasurer and Vice President
      - General, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 22)
      - Rating Agency Meetings, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 23-24)
        Standard and Poors; Moody's Investors Service.
      - WHCU, 1979-83 (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Vice President for Campus Affairs
      - General, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 26)
        Drug use at Cornell; Student Activities.
      - Campus Store, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 27)
      - Conference Director, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 28)
      - Cornell United Religious Work, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 29-31)
      - Center for Religion, Ethics and Social Policy, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 32-33)
      - Dean of Students, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 34)
      - Dean of Students, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 35)
        Counseling and advising programs.
      - Dining, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 36)
      - Housing, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 37-38)
      - Housing, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 39)
        Fraternities; Sororities.
      - Housing, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 40)
        Committee on Residential Learning.
      - International Student Office, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 41)
      - Department of Public Safety (DPS), 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 42)
      - DPS - Contingency Planning, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 43)
      - DPS - Policies, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 44)
      - Transportation, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 45-46)
      - University Health Services, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 47)
      - University Unions, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 48)
    - Vice President for Facilities and Business Operations
      - General, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 49)
      - Critical Maintenance, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 50)
      - Energy Conservation, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 51)
      - Department of Environmental Conservation, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 52)
      - Facilities Resource Allocation Committee, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 53-59)
      - General Services, 1983-84 (Box 91, Folder 60)
      - Insurance, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Life Safety Services, 1983-84 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Planning and Facilities, 1983-84 (Box 92, Folder 3-4)
      - Real Estate, 1983-84 (Box 92, Folder 5-6)
    - Vice President for Public Affairs
      - General, 1983-84 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - General, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 8)
        Token gifts for formal festivities.
      - General, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 9)
        Public Affairs objectives.
      - Alumni - General, 1983-84 (Box 92, Folder 10-12)
      - Alumni - General, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 13)
        Reunion schedule.
      - Alumni - General, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 14)
        Cornell Association of Class Officers.
      - Cornell Alumni News, 1983-84 (Box 92, Folder 15)
      - Cornell Adult University, 1983-84 (Box 92, Folder 16)